{
    "subject": "resource/11th_Ohio_Cavalry",
    "predicate": "ontology/notableCommander",
    "object": "resource/William_O._Collins",
    "human_readable": "The 11th Ohio Cavalry had a notable commander, William O. Collins.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9735003709793091,
            "question": "Who was the commander of the 11th Ohio Cavalry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8232361078262329,
            "question": "Which cavalry unit did William O. Collins lead?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8053631782531738,
            "question": "Was William O. Collins a notable figure in military history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.75306636095047,
            "question": "What are some examples of notable battles or campaigns involving the 11th Ohio Cavalry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7422150373458862,
            "question": "Were there any significant achievements or actions associated with William O. Collins's command?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7203124761581421,
            "question": "What was William O. Collins known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5848014950752258,
            "question": "How is William O. Collins remembered in military history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5773869752883911,
            "question": "What historical context can help us understand the role of the 11th Ohio Cavalry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5303741097450256,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about William O. Collins's military career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5237480401992798,
            "question": "In what war or conflict might the 11th Ohio Cavalry have participated?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The 11th Ohio Cavalry had a notable commander, William O. Collins.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7566_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about William O. Collins's military career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7566_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What historical context can help us understand the role of the 11th Ohio Cavalry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7566_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is William O. Collins remembered in military history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7566_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7566_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7566_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7566_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7566_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7566_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7566_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7566_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7566_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7566_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7566_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the documents, William O. Collins was indeed a notable commander of the 11th Ohio Cavalry, as mentioned in several texts (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7566/re-ranker-msmarco/44.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7566/re-ranker-msmarco/56.txt, and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7566/re-ranker-msmarco/78.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about William O. Collins commanding the 11th Ohio Volunteer Cavalry and being involved in military actions related to Fort Laramie and other locations during the Civil War era, which supports the statement that he was a notable commander of the 11th Ohio Cavalry."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}